<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mastr</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mastr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>| © Mastr</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>C Programming Tutorials in Nepali</title>
      <link>/post/c-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/c-programming/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Start learning C programming now in nepali language.
C is a general-purpose computer programming language. It was created in the 1970s by Dennis Ritchie at Bell Labs, and remains very widely used and influential. By design, C&#39;s features cleanly reflect the capabilities of the targetted CPUs.
Click here to get your hands on learning.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch videos</title>
      <link>/post/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/videos/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Watch and subscribe us on youtube to get interesting and simplified tutorials and videos
How to swap 2 numbers without using 3 variables | Swapping numbers in C++ Get connected with me on twitter The competition will end soon. pic.twitter.com/XecZmMhRBO
&amp;mdash; Satya Raj Awasthi (@SatyaRajAwasth1) August 10, 2022 
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Notices</title>
      <link>/post/notices/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/notices/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            The &amp;quot;Notices&amp;quot; shortcode enables you to call out pieces of information - sidebars, warnings, tips, etc.
To create a notice on a page, you can use the notice shortcode.
You use the notice shortcode, with the first parameter being one of note, info, tip, and warning. Then add a title for your note in quotes as the second parameter. The inner body of the note can be whatever markdown you want to create.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
